mr-guangdong.com 2016-11-29

# Security and Privacy

Welcome to Mr-world, your reliable online marketplace. 

The web site identified by the uniform resource locator www.Mr-world.com (the “ **Site** ”) is provided by Mr-world Holding (“ **Mr-world** ”) as a service to our customers. This Security and Privacy Policy (the “ **Agreement** ” or “ **Policy** ”) is entered into between you as a registered user of the site (“ **Registered User** ”) and Mr-world.

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we value your trust highly. We will not sell or loan your personal information to a third party under any circumstances. We will work hard to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use such information as we have described herein. 

By your use and access of the Site, you accept this Security and Privacy Policy.

**What personal information do we collect?**

You may choose to use or access our Site without revealing any personal and transactional information about yourself, but you will need to register and create an account in order to make a purchase or take advantage of certain feature and functions, including, but not limited to, “Save for Later” and “Address Book”. If you provide us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of the information on our server located in the People’s Republic of China (the “ **P.R.C.** ”).

As set forth in more detail below, Mr-world collects personal information that you provide when using the Site. This information includes your first and last name, email address, a password and other information required when you create your Mr-world account or when you participate in or conduct surveys and contests via the Site, email, or other media of Mr-world. In order to protect your confidentiality and verify your identity, we may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service Department. 

In addition to the personal information we may collect and process during registration and any surveys, we also collect, store and process the following information about our users:

1\. Purchase Information 

When you make a purchase from Mr-world, we collect your name and payment method information. When you create an account at Mr-world, you can choose to save your billing information in “My Mr-world.” You can also save one or more shipping addresses in your Mr-world Address Book. 

2\. Services Account Information 

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the Mr-world services, including but not limited to, Mr-world’s Transaction Platform. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at Mr-world. 

3\. Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you visit the Site, you will be assigned a permanent “cookie” (a small text file) to be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit the Site so that we can enhance and customize your online purchasing experience.

You can choose to browse on the Site without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of the Site. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and providing a more personalized future shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to the Site. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to the Site and will not sell or loan this information to any third parties. 

We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers’ activities on the Site and to track and measure the performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties.

4\. Publishing Information

When you submit any information on the Site during your use or access, including, but not limited to, information on the Mr-world blog, the rating system, or product catalog, you are deemed to have given your permission to Mr-world to publish such information, and Mr-world and the Site hereby enjoy an irrevocable, perpetual, worldwide and royalty-free, sub-licensable license to use all information provided by such user to exercise the copyright, compilation, database and publicity rights any user has in such material or information, in any media form. 

**How we use your personal information?**

We do not sell, loan, trade or exchange any user’s personal information without such user’s consent. The information we collect on the Site may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

  * Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online;
  * Register you as a member of Mr-world;
  * Prevent fraud;
  * Confirm your orders;
  * Resolve disputes and prevent prohibited and illegal activities;
  * Enforce our Terms of Use and related agreements;
  * Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests;
  * Communicate great values and featured items to you;
  * Find and stock the products you want; and
  * Customize, measure and improve our services and your purchase experience.

**When and with whom can we share your personal information?**

We do not sell or loan your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share your personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including, but not limited to, fulfilling customer orders, offering certain products and services in connection with the Site, communicating to customers, providing customer service, storing, sharing and retrieving customers’ photo images in our Photo Center, enhancing and improving clients’ purchase experience, enabling access to our partners’ web sites, providing a personalized purchase experience and preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. 

Aside from the purposes described above, we will not share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or there are special circumstances, such as when Mr-world is required by the government, law enforcement body, obligee whose legitimate right has been injured, subpoena or other legal document to share such information, or if we believe it to be reasonably necessary to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Mr-world’s rights or property. We may also share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**How can you control the use of your personal information?**

You can modify or delete your personal information at any time. Simply go to My Mr-world. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete your personal information at your discretion. How can we protect the security of your personal information? 

Your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account on the Site (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of Mr-world will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it at anytime by going to My Mr-world. Log in with your email address and password, then click “Change Name, Email & Password” and enter a new password. 

**Minors**

Mr-world does not intentionally collect personal information about minors or other persons without full civil conduct capacity, but based on the properties of Internet, there is no way for Mr-world and the Site to distinguish the age or capacity of the users. By accepting this Agreement through your use or access of the Site, you certify that you are a person over 18 years old with full capacity and ability to form a legally binding contract in the jurisdiction in which you are resident or in which you are entering into this Agreement. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the terms of this Agreement, do not use the Site. 

Meanwhile, if a minor or other person does not have full civil conduct capacity and has provided personal information to us without the proper consent of their parent or legal guardian, such parent or legal guardian should contact us to remove such personal information. 

**Security**

Your information is stored on our servers located in the P.R.C, and we adopt lots of tools, means and technologies to protect them against unauthorized access, use and disclosure. For instance, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet. However, we are limited in our efforts by the technologies currently available, and no data transmission or storage over Internet can be guaranteed to be perfectly safe. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your information and privacy, we do not promise or guarantee that your information will always be private and safe. 

**General**

We realize that making purchases on the Site, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly and pledge to you, our clients that we will work hard to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address or checking account information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally. 

Mr-world may provide links to certain third party web sites. This Security and Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on the Site. Other web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security. We encourage you to review the privacy policies on these sites before you use and access them. You are solely responsible for your use and access of other web sites. 

Mr-world will obtain your consent before allowing the download of any software from the Site, and Mr-world will not automatically download any software to your computer system. Once you consent to the initial download of any software, you may receive automatic updates or patches pertaining to such software. You understand and agree that any material, including but not limited to downloaded software, required or automated updates, modifications, reinstallations, or software otherwise obtained through the use of the Site is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damages to your computer system or loss of data that may result from any such material. 

Mr-world reserves the right to update or modify this Security and Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you. The most current version of the Policy will govern Mr-world’s use of the information and will always be at http://help.Mr-world.com/help/buyer_about. If Mr-world makes a change that, in Mr-world’s sole discretion, is material, Mr-world will notify you via e-mail to the email address associated with your account. Your use of the Site following any such change constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by the Security and Privacy Policy as amended. 

Mr-world may transfer this Policy and all or part of its rights, obligations and interests to any party or entity in its sole discretion; however, a User may not assign its rights, obligations and interests under this Policy to any party or entity. 

Terms which have not been defined or stipulated in this Agreement shall be interpreted in accordance with the definition(s) or provision(s) of the Terms of Use of Mr-world.
